twentyfeet.com 2015-03-20

# Privacy Policy | SumAll

At SumAll Inc. we’re all about transparency and are excited that you’ve taken time to read our privacy policy. Here you’ll be able to find all you need on how we collect, use and share your information.

SumAll Inc. (“SumAll”) is committed to protecting your privacy and the privacy of your customers. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe to you our practices regarding the collection and use of data from users of our website, located at [sumall.com](https://sumall.com/) (“Site”), and related Services (as defined in the Terms of Use). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. If you simply browse the Site you are referred to in this Privacy Policy as a “Visitor.” If you have registered with the Site and receive Services you are referred to in this Privacy Policy as a “Subscriber.” Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meanings given in our Terms of Use located at [sumall.com/terms](https://sumall.com/terms).

**TRUSTe online privacy certification**

#### **DigiCert Seal**

SumAll has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software or software APIs. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this website, [sumall.com](https://sumall.com/).

TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [support@sumall.com](mailto:support@sumall.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

**Generally, SumAll collects the following types of information:**

**Visitor Data & Anonymous Visitor Data:** When we refer to “Visitor Data” we mean data that allows someone to identify or contact a Visitor, including, for example, their name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any other non-public information about them that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data. When we refer to “Anonymous Visitor Data” we mean data that is not used, or intended to be used, to identify a particular Visitor.

**Subscriber Data & Anonymous Subscriber Data:** When we refer to “Subscriber Data” we mean data that allows someone to identify or contact a Subscriber, including, for example, their name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any other non-public information about them that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data. When we refer to “Anonymous Subscriber Data” we mean data that is not used, or intended to be used, to identify a particular Subscriber.

**Crazy Awesome Data & Anonymous Crazy Awesome Data:** When we refer to “Crazy Awesome Data” we mean all other data that relates to the Subscriber, the Subscriber’s business, or customers of the Subscriber and is not publicly available. This category of information can include but is not limited to data about a Subscriber such as exercise history, social media activities, or bank account information; data that is proprietary to the Subscriber’s business, including but not limited to figures and other data related to their business’s sales, revenue, costs, vendors, customers, inventory, website traffic, marketing activities, and social media activities; and/or personally identifiable information about the customers of a Subscriber or their business. When we refer to “Anonymous Crazy Awesome Data” we mean data that is not used, or intended to be used, to identify a particular Subscriber, their business, or a customer of a Subscriber.

**Subscriber Data vs Crazy Awesome Data:** When you give us your name or email address, for example, either during sign-up or contact with a customer service agent, then you are explicitly telling us who you are and the data is considered Subscriber Data. When you provide us with information about a bank account, however, we don’t know if it’s your bank account, your business’s account, or the account of your daughter, and as such it’s Crazy Awesome Data rather than Subscriber Data. In general all data is that is not explicitly Visitor Data or Subscriber Data, including most data provided via APIs and third parties, is considered Crazy Awesome Data.

Visitor Data, Subscriber Data and Crazy Awesome Data may be referred to herein collectively as “Personal Data.” Anonymous Visitor Data, Anonymous Subscriber Data and Anonymous Crazy Awesome Data may be referred to herein collectively as “Anonymous Data.”

## 1\. User Consent

By using our Site or Services you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## 2\. A Note to Users Outside of the United States

Your Visitor Data, Subscriber Data or Crazy Awesome Data, as applicable, may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in other countries, including the United States, where laws regarding processing of personal data may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

## 3\. How we Collect Personal Data

We collect Personal Visitor, Subscriber and Crazy Awesome Data as described below:

**I.  Most Subscriber Data is Directly Provided to Us by You**

When you provide us feedback or contact us via e-mail we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other content included in the e-mail, in order to send you a reply. We may collect your first and last name, e-mail address, physical address, phone number, business name, and password when you create an Account. We may collect Personal Data on the Site when we make clear that we are collecting it and you voluntarily provide it, for example, when you add additional services to your account. We also collect other types of data that you provide to us voluntarily, such as your operating system and version, product registration number, and other requested information if you contact us regarding support for the Services. We retain information on your behalf, such as files and messages that you store using your Account.

**II.  Most Crazy Awesome Data is Acquired via APIs**

We may collect Crazy Awesome Data directly from you through the Site. We may also receive Crazy Awesome Data about you, your business or your customers from our partners, including our platform partners such as Shopify, Authorize, MailChimp, Facebook, and Google that may provide services to you or your business. This information may include various proprietary data relating to your business. This information may be shared with us manually or automatically through the establishment of an application programming interface (API) with our partner. We may add this information to the Crazy Awesome Data we have already collected from you via our Site in order to improve the Services we provide.

**III.  Most Visitor Data is Collected Through Technology**

To make our Site more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) collect information from you, including your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session), domain name, and/or a date/time stamp for your visit.

We also use cookies and URL information to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the information for which you searched and viewed. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Site. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions, however, please note that certain aspects of the Site or Services may not be available if the Persistent Cookies are removed.

## 4\. What We Do With Personal Data

**I. Use of Subscriber and Visitor Data**

In general, Subscriber and Visitor Data are used either to respond to requests that you make or to aid us in serving you better. We use such Personal Data in the following ways:

  * to facilitate the creation and security of your Account on our network;
  * identify you as a user in our system;
  * provide improved administration of our Site and Services;
  * provide the Services you request;
  * improve the quality of experience when you interact with our Site and Services;
  * send you a welcome e-mail to verify ownership of the e-mail address provided when your Account was created;
  * send you administrative e-mail notifications such as security or support and maintenance advisories;
  * respond to your inquiries related to employment opportunities or other requests;
  * to make telephone calls to you, from time to time, as a part of secondary fraud protection or to solicit your feedback; and
  * to send newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials related to our Services and for other marketing purposes.

**II. Use of Crazy Awesome Data**

Unless we have a separate authorization from the data subject, we will not use the Crazy Awesome Data we collect for any reason other than to provide the Services the Subscriber requests and improve the quality of experience when the Subscriber interacts with our Site or Services. For illustration purposes only, we may use the name of a Subscriber’s customer to help the Subscriber analyze that particular customer’s spending habits as part of our Services, but we will never contact that customer directly for marketing purposes.

**III. Use of Data by Third Party Service Providers**

We may use third party service providers to help us analyze certain online activities. For example, these service providers may help us measure the performance of our online campaigns or analyze visitor activity on the Site. We may permit these service providers to use cookies and other technologies to perform these services for us. The use of cookies by third parties is not covered by our PP. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

## 5\. Information You Share

Our service includes a number of means by which you may share data with third parties, including, but not limited to, directly within the site, through the generation of content on media sites, such as Facebook or Twitter, and through email or SMS creation and transmission. In all such cases, it is you, rather than SumAll, who is sharing the data, and, as such, you are responsible for any Personal Data that you expose through such sharing.

Be aware of what you are sharing and who you are sharing it with.

## 6\. Anonymous Data

We may create Anonymous Data records from Visitor, Subscriber and Crazy Awesome Data by subjecting it to de-identification through the removal of all personally identifying data (including, but not limited to, names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses) and through the use of generally accepted statistical de-identification techniques.

SumAll may use Anonymous Data, for illustration purposes only, to generate benchmarks and indices as part of our Service, to issue a press release as to the total revenue amount of our U.S. customers, to produce analysis of shopping cart abandonment rates, or to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content of our Services and improve Site navigation. SumAll reserves the right to use Anonymous Data for any purpose and disclose Anonymous Data to third parties at its sole discretion.

## 7\. Advertising

We partner with a third party ad network to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites to provide you with targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by [clicking here](http://preferences.truste.com/2.0/). Please note this does not prevent you from being served non-targeted advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

## 8\. Plaid Integration

SumAll allows you to retrieve bank and financial information through Plaid Technologies, Inc. (“Plaid”). As of today the following platform connections are done through Plaid: American Express, Bank of America, Chase, Citi, US Bank, USAA, and Wells Fargo. If you make a connection to these or any other banks or financial services through the SumAll Service you expressly acknowledge and agree that such information will be treated by Plaid in accordance with the Plaid Privacy Policy located [here](https://plaid.com/privacy/#Docs_Privacy_Policy).

## 9\. Access and Control of Your Personal Data

**Choice**

We will periodically send you free newsletters and e-mails that directly promote the use of our Site or Services. When you receive newsletters or promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly at [support@sumall.com](mailto:support@sumall.com). Even if you opt-out of receiving marketing related email messages, we will continue to send you service related communications, including notices related to your Account or any updates to our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy.

**Changes to Personal Data**

You may change any of your Personal Data in your Account by editing your profile within your Account or by sending an e-mail to us at [support@sumall.com](mailto:support@sumall.com). You may request deletion of your Personal Data by us, but please note that we may be required to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete any information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## 10\. Disclosure of Personal Data

We disclose your Personal Data as described below and as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

In order to perform Services, we may contract with third party service providers, including service providers who may process payments on our behalf or provide technical support. These third parties may have access to user data required to perform their functions. All such parties are required to enter into a written agreement with us that they will not use the user data for any purpose other than to provide the services requested by SumAll.

**Affiliates and Acquisitions**

We may share some or all of your Personal Data with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (“Affiliates”) for market research or other purposes, in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires our company, business, or our assets (including in connection with a bankruptcy proceeding), that company will possess the Personal Data collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding the Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Other Disclosures**

Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Data (as described below), SumAll may disclose Personal Data if it believes in good faith that such disclosure is necessary (a) in connection with any legal investigation; (b) to comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on SumAll; (c) to protect or defend the rights or property of SumAll or users of the Services; and/or (d) to investigate or assist in preventing any violation or potential violation of the law, this Privacy Policy, or Terms of Use.

## 11\. Security of Your Personal Data

SumAll is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Data. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Data from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. When you enter information in our form fields, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while SumAll uses reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Data, SumAll cannot guarantee its absolute security. We also require you to enter a password to access your Account information. Please do not disclose your Account password to unauthorized people.

## 12\. Additional Information

**3rd Party Websites**

When you click on a link to any other website or location, you will leave our Site and go to another site and another entity may collect Personal Data or Anonymous Data from you. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of data after you click on links to such outside websites.

**Blog/Forum**

Our website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [support@sumall.com](mailto:support@sumall.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Testimonials**

With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [support@sumall.com](mailto:support@sumall.com).

**Social Media Buttons/Widgets**

Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Google +1 button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## 13\. Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any material changes in the way we use your Personal Data, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our Site. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our Site. These changes will be effective immediately for new users of our Service or as otherwise provided in the revised policy. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your Personal Data to provide us with your most current e-mail address.

In the event that the last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of Personal Data that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your Personal Data, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your Account with us. Continued use of our Site or Service, following notice of such changes, shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

## 14\. Contact Information

SumAll welcomes your comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy. Please e-mail us at [support@sumall.com](mailto:support@sumall.com) or contact us at the following address or phone number:

SumAll  
Attn: Matthew Law  
123 Williams St. 22nd floor  
New York, NY 10038  
+1 917 719 0255

We updated this on September 29, 2014. Your diligence is appreciated.
